{
    "id": "7d5756a866374327927889ec83c75520",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They have been informed by us. We …………………………… them.",
            "description": "The active verb in the present perfect has the form: have/have + past participle.",
            "answers": [
                "are informed",
                "have informed",
                "informed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The milk was drunk by the cat. The cat …………………………. the milk.",
            "description": "Was drunk is the passive form of drank. ",
            "answers": [
                "has drunk",
                "drank",
                "drunk"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The missing child has been found. They ………………………….. the missing child.",
            "description": "Has been found is the passive form of has/have found. ",
            "answers": [
                "found",
                "has found",
                "have found"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured were taken to hospital. They …………………………… the injured to hospital.",
            "description": "Were taken is the passive form of took.",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "have taken",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The winners were praised by all. All people ………………………………. the winners.",
            "description": "Were praised is the passive form of praised. ",
            "answers": [
                "have praised",
                "praised",
                "are praising"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The hall is being decorated. They ……………………………… the hall.",
            "description": "Is being decorated is the passive form of is/are decorating.",
            "answers": [
                "decorating",
                "are decorating",
                "have decorated"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The man was bitten by the dog. The dog ……………………….. the man.",
            "description": "Was bitten is the passive form of bit. ",
            "answers": [
                "bitten",
                "has bitten",
                "bit"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A large house is owned by her. She ……………………………. a large house.",
            "description": "Is owned is the passive form of own/owns.",
            "answers": [
                "owns",
                "is owning",
                "has owned"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A laptop was bought by her. She ………………………….. a laptop.",
            "description": "Was bought is the passive form of bought. ",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "has bought",
                "had bought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The match will be won by us. We …………………………….. the match.",
            "description": "Will be won is the passive form of will win. ",
            "answers": [
                "will be winning",
                "will win",
                "would win"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The house is being built. They ……………………………. the house.",
            "description": "Is being built is the passive form of is/are building. ",
            "answers": [
                "building",
                "are building",
                "are being built"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is being investigated. We …………………………………. it.",
            "description": "Is being investigated is the passive form of is / are investigating. ",
            "answers": [
                "are investigating",
                "are investigated",
                "investigated"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}